[Theme song]
[Meaningful music]
[lighter clicks]
[Italian]
Did Paolo send you?
maybe
[Meaningful music]
[Enzo's powerful moans]
[Vincenzo’s groans of difficulty]
[groans with difficulty]
[laughter]
Paolo Boss told me
If you show respect
(Enzo)
Kill me without pain
[laughter]
Tell it to Paolo
Even my soul won't respect you
[laughter]
[A pigeon cries is heard]
[Mysterious Music]
[Dove cries]
[Rhythmic music]
[gunshot]
[Fight noisily]
[Killer's Scream]
[gunshot]
[Rough breathing]
[sigh]
[Dove cries]
Insagi?
[Inspiring music]
Insagi
[Dove cries]
[surprised gasp]
[sigh]
(Chayoung)
[Korean]
Uh, have you cleaned everything up?
(Vincenzo)
Ah, ah, yeah
[Chayoung responds]
Ah, lawyer.
Shall we go to the office and have a drink?
There was pigeon poop on top...
Don't even talk
Oh, give it to me, I'll do it
Is that what Inzaki and his friends are like?
[elegant music]
Insagi
It's not that kind of pigeon.
Other things must have been like that.
Don't talk nonsense
(Vincenzo)
Insagi must be sad
Why are your clothes like this?
Ah, this
I guess the table got scratched by a nail while moving it.
- (Vincenzo) Ouch
- Oh, why are you moving it alone?
(Chayoung)
Just stand and drink, whatever.
Hey, lawyer.
[Chayoung’s embarrassed groan]
(Vincenzo)
My knees are sore
Let's sit down and have a drink, okay?
[Vincenzo’s groans in pain]
yes
[Chayoung clears her throat]
(Vincenzo)
Ah, the file taken out of that gallery.
You sent it to Prosecutor Jeong, right?
(Chayoung)
Yes, I'm probably excited and going to catch it.
(Vincenzo)
Oh, great.
(Chinese book)
No, why is it useless?
Do something like an event
Do you make things happen like this?
[Meaningful music]
Is the gallery your amusement park?
[Director Jeong’s trembling breathing]
(Director Jeong)
sorry
I really committed a deadly sin
It won't end with just you dying, me!
[Hanseo shouts]
(Junwoo)
Be quiet.
I'm thinking about you
Isn’t this so ridiculous, brother?
No thoughts at all, no thoughts!
Before the president is banned from leaving the country
I think you'd better get out.
(Chinese book)
Why, where?
Anyway, I
I'm going to take your place in your brother's place, why?
(Myunghee)
Evidence obtained from over there now
It's all directed at the president.
Sent to the Chairman's house from here
All IP records will appear.
vice president
going to new york
Find out the fastest plane
(Chinese book)
yes
[The door opens and closes]
[sigh]
[Junwoo’s angry groan]
[intense music]
[Director Jeong sobs]
[Junwoo’s powerful moans]
[Junwoo’s angry groan]
[Sobbing]
[Junwoo’s heavy breathing]
(Junwoo)
Even if I go when I go
I have to go see Vincenzo’s body.
[heavy music]
Yes, I've finished organizing it.
But one guy’s cell phone reception records say
(Hwang Gyu)
I have lawyer Choi Myung-hee's number.
[laughter]
[Puts down the wine bottle]
[Raising the glass]
Okay, good job, take care of it.
[Call connection tone]
[Italian]
Yes, consiglieri.
Luca!
“Nothing”
[Sobbing]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Korean]
You couldn’t kill me again?
It's hard to see Vincenzo's body even once.
[laughter]
[Director Jeong sobs]
No, what kind of mafia killers are like this?
(Chinese book)
What is this, ‘Home Alone’
Not a villain
What are these feathers?
Choi Myung-hee!
Lawyer
[nervous music]
[Myunghee takes a breath]
(Myunghee)
sorry
Let’s go to the airport quickly.
I will take care of you
[Siren sounds]
(Chinese book)
Stop that, quickly.
(Junwoo)
That's enough
[Meaningful music]
(Prosecutor Jeong)
It was a monumental day so I came out in person.
You look like you’re feeling a lot better, huh?
It's nothing bad
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Take me with you
I'll follow along as soon as it's sorted out.
[Music that heightens the mood]
[Dove cries]
[sigh]
[Calm music]
Hey, Insagi
You can't believe it
Have you really returned the favor?
[Dove cries]
(Vincenzo)
Huh?
Is that it?
No way, no
What kind of pigeon saves people?
[laughter]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[sigh]
[Exciting music]
(Chayoung)
Media companies have embargoes
‘Chairman Jang Han-seok arrested’
'Tomorrow morning, prosecutor Jeong In-guk
'Announcement of investigation to the public'
[Groans of satisfaction]
[laughter]
[Italian]
Well done
[Korean]
pretty
Oh my, thank you
[Calm music]
(Chayoung)
There's a letter in there too?
(Gyeongja)
Ah, there
Go home and read this
[sigh]
[The door slams shut]
(Cheolwook and Yeonjin)
hello
(Yeonjin)
Oh my
(Cheolwook)
That guy, Chairman Babel
Let's all work together
It's almost like you got caught, right, lawyer?
yes, thanks to you all
Chairman Jang was caught and thrown in.
[People cheering]
[Calm music]
(Prosecutor on TV)
From now on, the Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office
Regarding Prosecutor Jeong In-guk’s Babel Group
(Joosung)
Okay, I guess I'll start now.
(Prosecutor on TV)
There will be a public investigation announcement.
(Prosecutor Jeong on TV)
hello
[Music that heightens the mood]
This is Prosecutor Jeong In-guk of the Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office.
[Camera shutter sounds repeatedly]
(Prosecutor Jeong)
For the past year I
Regarding Babel Group’s six charges
We have been investigating
It's all due to bad corporate corruption.
national economy and legal system
These were seriously damaging charges.
(Joosung)
Yes, yes, oh!
I feel refreshed inside
[People laughing]
(Prosecutor Jeong on TV)
But now to the people
I think I need to tell you the truth.
[The camera shutter sound on TV continues to sound]
Past Chairman Jang Kook-hwan
I'm filled with resonance
Babel Group was investigated excessively.
(Prosecutor Jeong on TV)
I was demoted
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Meaningful music]
about the past
I participated in the investigation with personal feelings.
With unproven facts
Babel Chairman Jang Han-seok
tried to prosecute
What are you talking about, that crazy bran?
(Prosecutor Jeong on TV)
And yesterday too
Babel Group due to excessive investigation
caused great damage
No, is that person Prosecutor Jeong?
I think it went over, Prosecutor Jeong.
(Heesu)
Did you betray that person?
[laughter]
(Prosecutor Jeong on TV)
This announcement today
With my confession of conscience
Trust in our Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office
It's for recovery.
From now on, no personal feelings will be involved.
With a clear investigation...
(Seunghyuk)
Ah, there is no twist like this.
[Prosecutor Jeong continues speaking on TV]
If something like this comes out in a drama
It's contrived, right?
드라마 이렇게 만들면 욕먹지
(TV 속 정 검사)
바벨그룹 장한석 회장님께
진심 어린 사과의 말씀을 전합니다
(준우)
괜찮아, 괜찮아
[함께 웃는다]
(한서)
아, 저 새끼, 저거 결국에 저러고
빌빌거릴 줄 알았습니다, 제가
아유, 저 시건방진 새끼
나한테도 인사해, 새끼야
I'm so greedy, Mr.
[Hanseo’s laughter]
Look at me groveling
(Prosecutor Jeong on TV)
As of today, all charges against Babel Group have been
Was acquitted
The investigation is scheduled to be concluded
We apologize for causing confusion to the public.
[laughter]
[People moan in surprise]
[Chayoung’s trembling breathing]
[Chayoung sighs]
[The door opens]
[sigh]
(Hongsik)
Oh my
[Yeonjin sighs]
(Vincenzo)
See you later, lawyer.
(Chayoung)
I have to go and give him a good slap.
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
(Vincenzo)
Even if we go, Prosecutor Jeong won’t let us meet.
See you later
This is really too much
No, the person who hated Babel so much
How in just one moment
[Calm music]
[sigh]
[Chayoung sighs]
(Chayoung)
No, why didn't we expect it?
[heavy music]
You can avoid flying knives, but
You can't avoid the hidden knife
Isn’t the lawyer angry?
angry
[sigh]
It's a lot
I'm just used to this situation.
Prosecutor Jeong will not leave you alone.
I'll pay you back somehow
Responding emotionally to betrayal
Only we lose
The bigger the betrayal
You have to deal with it carefully
[Vincenzo pats Chayoung]
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Hey, let's do this sooner rather than later.
Ugh
I'm sorry for being so reckless so far.
Chief Prosecutor
First of all, about two weeks as a formality.
I'll suspend you
Take a breath
[Meaningful music]
When I return, I will immediately start working as a manager.
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Oh, the room…
Oh, just use Director Seo’s room.
Write it comfortably
yes, thank you
Is there anything else you need?
me and my house
Please assign some bodyguards.
The mafia might be after me.
[laughter]
(Junwoo)
Aren't you leaving?
Evidence I secured today
(Prosecutor Jeong)
You know it's strong and certain, right?
I really can't get out this time.
But if I make it all go away
How high can I raise it?
[nervous music]
I'm sincerely asking this.
[Elasticity]
(Junwoo)
Oh, isn't this a hidden camera?
[Junwoo’s laughter]
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
The time has finally come
Then why until now
Did you bother me that much?
Just like today
Vincenzo
Because it brings you the best evidence.
I'll ask again
How high can I raise it?
To the Chief Prosecutor of the Southeastern District
Chief Prosecutor's Office
- more than
- (Junwoo) I’m too greedy.
Items that I am greedy for
If you have it
guillotine file
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Where is the guillotine file?
[Music that heightens the mood]
Do you know who you're with?
[English]
An absolute ring that will rule over everyone!
My Precious
[Junwoo’s laughter]
[Car door opens]
[Car door slams shut]
(Prosecutor Jeong)
[Korean]
Why are there no bodyguards?
[nervous music]
[The bodyguard groans with difficulty]
[Prosecutor Jeong’s surprised groan]
honey
Seungmin
Honey, Seungmin
honey
Seungmin, honey!
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Are you here?
dad!
[Prosecutor Jeong’s trembling breathing]
[Seungmin’s laughter]
[Music that heightens tension]
[Italian]
Hello, friend!
[Korean]
- (Seungmin) Dad
- (Prosecutor Jeong) Yes.
(Seungmin)
Dad's junior from Italy
So handsome
He's my ideal type
[Prosecutor Jeong’s wife’s laughter]
[Awkward laughter]
(Prosecutor Jeong)
We already tell them that guests are coming.
Mr. Vincenzo did all the cooking.
(Seungmin)
Yeah, the spaghetti was so delicious.
(Prosecutor Jeong)
[Laughing awkwardly]
Did you do that?
(Seungmin)
Yeah
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Seungmin
(Vincenzo)
Senior, what about meals?
Seungmin, dad still
I guess you haven't eaten
Please sit down, senior.
We have a lot to talk about
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Sit down now, baby
Yeah
[Meaningful music]
(Vincenzo)
Seungmin
My dad too
Shall I make you some delicious spaghetti?
(Seungmin)
yes
[Prosecutor Jeong’s wife’s laughter]
(Vincenzo)
Can Seungmin help you?
(Prosecutor Jeong)
I don't mind killing me
Please don't touch my wife and daughter.
(Vincenzo)
don't worry
Because I'm not a person like you
How can I live now
Is there any?
Well, I'll do anything.
When people become really evil
Do you know what that standard is?
(Vincenzo)
whatever you do
It's time to know no shame
You've passed that standard now
please
(Prosecutor Jeong)
please save me
[laughter]
(Vincenzo)
I have no intention of killing you yet.
Killing a traitor early
Because it is the highest tolerance
[shaking breathing]
[Prosecutor Jeong’s groans of difficulty]
[Prosecutor Jeong’s frightened groan]
do whatever you want
When you have everything
I will kill you then
[Prosecutor Jeong chuckles]
Ah
And sometimes Seungmin feeds me some pasta.
Every time I eat out
Dad says he only eats what he likes
There were a lot of complaints
[Prosecutor Jeong’s trembling breathing]
[shaking breathing]
[Prosecutor Jeong chuckles]
[Prosecutor Jeong’s heavy breathing]
(Junwoo)
vice president
Tomorrow, with Mr. Jeongbae of Daechang Ilbo
Make some space
(Chinese book)
I'm having a hard time with that guy, Jeongbae.
[sigh]
For some reason
Can I ask you something?
Advance into electric vehicles
About Babel Chemical’s battery production
I want to talk about a planned article.
That's on the level of Director Cheon.
Wouldn't it be possible?
Not as director
I'm doing this to raise Babel Chemical's stock price.
I need to talk to the boss.
Um, but
[Meaningful music]
We still have plans
I don't have any skills...
We're not talking about making a real car.
If the stock price rises and falls, it's over.
(Chinese book)
Wow
As expected, your brain is really
Ugh, I can't handle it.
Hey, don't talk nonsense.
(Junwoo)
What is that
Just take care of the Ragusaeng enema.
If you go somewhere and talk nonsense
Because it doesn't work, okay?
Let's do it well, do it well, do it well
[Junwoo sighs]
[The door clicks open]
[The door clicks shut]
Ha, really, the setup went well today.
[Cheolwook clears his throat]
[Yeonjin’s excited moans]
[sigh]
[Hongsik puts down his chopsticks]
Ever since that prosecutor's bastard betrayed me
I can't sleep very much
(Hongsik)
Why are you like this?
(Cheolwook)
Right?
[Yeonjin responds]
I don't think it has anything to do with us.
I feel strangely upset and bad
(Heesu)
Do you know why that is?
(Yeonjin)
Why?
What we do in the world
It's because I'm being crazy.
[Calm music]
In the past, I was just trying to make a living.
Things I wasn't even interested in
It feels like it's all my work
[Cheolwook’s elasticity]
That's what I heard
No, if it were like before, it would be a chaebol and the law.
Oh, what does it have to do with us?
(Heesu)
yes
(Hongsik)
I’m also a guy with short bag straps.
I know what's going wrong these days
(Youngho)
Uncle Vincenzo
You said this when I was giving you true education.
We become what we think
If I think of myself as strong, I become strong.
Wow, it’s so cool, right?
Anyway, I
According to our lawyer Vincenzo,
I will keep fighting
- Yes
- (Yeonjin) Yes
Instead, don't cause an accident.
We might become three now...
(Heesu)
What is it?
Have you two really changed your mind?
We are now trying to prepare for the second generation.
- (Hee-su) Mom, mom, mom
- (Hongsik) Oh my, I’m sorry, I’m sorry
eat meat, eat meat
[Hee-su cries]
Oh my, that way, the two of you will argue less.
It looks good, oh my
[People laughing]
(Cheolwook)
thank you
- (Hongsik) Hey, listen more, listen, listen more
- (Cheolwook) Why are you laughing?
(Heesu)
Oh, that's great, right?
Well thought out
[Cheolwook’s laughter]
[Atmospheric music plays]
(Chayoung)
um
It's pretty
Lawyer
How do you feel?
(Vincenzo)
It's good
[Vincenzo laughs slightly]
But I went shopping last time.
Wasn't it enough?
I'm not writing this
I'm choosing a gift for Ms. Oh Kyeong-ja.
Before it gets any worse
I'll take you out once.
(Vincenzo)
Ah…
Wouldn’t that be too much?
(Chayoung)
According to the doctor
They say it's okay for an hour or two.
It's been a while since you're going out, so I need to decorate.
Please also choose a lawyer.
You have discernment.
[bright music]
(Chayoung)
Because the lawyer bought this
Attorney, please give it to your mother directly.
(Vincenzo)
Okay, the lawyer will give it to you...
yes?
What are you surprised about?
I'm giving it to my mother.
Did lawyer Hong Yoo-chan talk about it?
no
My father is a client secret
I never tell my daughter.
But how did you know?
Pay all the hospital bills
(Chayoung)
While I hate you so much
Get revenge on Shinkwang Bank
Know how to distinguish between bungeoppang and carp bread
Anyone can see that he is Oh Kyung-ja's son, right?
[Calm music]
[Sighing]
Me
Getting involved in other people's family problems
I really hate it
I'll be a bit rude just once.
Why don't you tell your mother quickly?
The lawyer knows.
There really isn't much left.
One day for my mother
It's not just one day
told me
Regret is the greatest hell one can experience in life.
That was right.
Please, lawyer
I don't want you to go through that kind of hell.
[Clinks the glass]
[Laughs slightly]
[Clears cough]
[Puts down the glass]
[Gyeongja’s surprised gasp]
(Gyeongja)
Wow, this is so sophisticated.
This is too much
Thank you so much, lawyer.
It's no big deal
The lawyer chose it for an hour.
(Gyeongja)
Yes?
[Chayoung’s laughter]
Oh my, why did you go to such lengths?
Me, but
What kind of outing am I going to do?
I'm not feeling well either
I can't do it because it's too much trouble for you two.
Oh, not me on the day I go out.
(Chayoung)
The lawyer will take you out.
Right?
yes
You're busy, but it's because of me
[Chayoung’s moans of denial]
No
If there is a place you want to go
Feel free to think about it.
yes
(Chayoung)
Rest now, let's go
(Vincenzo)
Yeah
(Gyeongja)
Lawyer
I have something to tell you.
my case
I want to apply for a retrial
Really?
yes
Why did you suddenly change your mind?
fact
There is a day when I don't want to apply for a retrial.
There wasn't
[Calm music]
(Gyeongja)
I wanted to do it every day
But
I hesitated
I couldn't muster up the courage.
But
Now that death is near
I barely have the courage
Can I ask you a favor?
Can you listen?
What do you think, lawyer?
I will follow your wishes.
yes
I'm applying for a retrial.
[Chayoung laughs slightly]
I'll get ready right away
thank you
thank you so much
[Gyeongja sighs]
[Laughs slightly]
(President Oh)
And the president passed away
How can you not come once?
You son of a bitch
[Junwoo’s awkward laugh]
[President Oh’s laughter]
(Junwoo)
Oh, I'm sorry, mister.
I'm out of my mind.
[laughter]
Why are you making such a fuss about management, huh?
(President Oh)
For covering you
Our TV Daechang is having a hard time
I'll pay it all back, man.
[laughter]
Did you hear what Hanseo said?
(President Oh)
Yeah
Uh, Babel Chemical battery-related special article.
[Meaningful music]
But Hanseok
These days, even elementary school students buy stocks.
Articles like this are sensitive and dangerous.
[Laughs slightly]
You did it all for your father too.
You can do the same.
No, this beautiful person
What prompted you to run away so quickly at night?
[sigh]
[Interesting music]
I
I made a big mistake
(Director Jeong)
Even if you sacrifice your life, it won't be solved
[Seokdo’s sad groan]
It's such a pity
don't worry too much
(Seokdo)
There was just one seat available.
Right now
I think you can fly
All the way to Taiwan
You're going right away, right?
Yes, of course
Because the wind is nice today
Fly straight to Cebu
Even in detail
Can you fly further without stopping?
[laughter]
There's a bit of a tendency to get hit and miss with this one.
If you don't like it, you don't have to go.
- (Seokdo) Hey…
- (Director Jeong) Oh, no, no.
(Seokdo)
yes, contract
Please read through
[Message notification sound]
(Miss Miss)
Uh, huh?
(Seokdo)
Hey, there are guests here now, why, what?
Tsk
(Miss Miss)
The stock room Jirashi appeared.
Daechang Ilbo will launch Babel Chemicals
They say they are preparing a planned article.
Regarding electric vehicles and batteries.
[Interesting music]
(Seokdo)
Wait a minute, yes, read on.
[Director Jeong responds]
I need to quickly include Babel Chemistry, then.
[Chayoung’s angry groan]
[Slams the desk]
[Joosung and Chayoung sigh]
(Chayoung)
Babel these things never die
You're getting richer and richer
Why? why?
[Vincenzo clears his throat]
[Chayoung sighs]
(Vincenzo)
Hey ladies and gentlemen
Would you like to have a cup of coffee with us?
I don't feel like drinking coffee right now
I’m not in the mood for coffee right now either.
Tsk, yeah
[Interesting music]
[Chayoung sighs in frustration]
Ah, Prosecutor Jeong, this traitorous bastard, Mr.
Because of that bastard
The barbell only gets stronger
(Chayoung)
No, because I visited yesterday.
Make them pay, why?
I'm planning to pay in installments.
[Savoring moans]
(Joosung)
Maybe
Isn’t Prosecutor Jeong intentionally putting on a show?
Infiltrate inside the enemy
Trying to uncover all the corruption...
(Vincenzo)
Well, here, Mr. Secretary.
(Chayoung)
Republic of Korea Constitutional Thought
There has never been a single prosecutor like that.
[Vincenzo laughs]
(Vincenzo)
We don't need a prosecutor.
[Joosung sighs]
What is that again?
[Vincenzo’s elasticity]
(Vincenzo)
Oh, this?
It's a guillotine file.
[Exciting music]
guillotine file
That
I accidentally put it in a secret room.
You said it was closed...
- Who? Me?
- (Joosung) Yes
Was it like that?
[laughter]
[Sharp sound effect]
[surprised gasp]
[Chayoung pulls out a chair]
[Juseong’s elasticity]
(Chayoung)
Hey
This gentleman
Vincenzo Cassano
(Joosung)
I'll throw away this guillotine file to the world.
If you solve this on the internet, you can do it within an hour.
It spreads all over the world
- (Chayoung) That’s not it.
- Why?
(Vincenzo)
It'll be noisy for a few days, but
Not a single person will pay for their sins.
This is to reveal the truth
It wasn't made
For the villain to exploit the villain's weakness
It was made
only the villain
I can use it properly
(Chayoung)
We can use it like that too.
Like inserting a straw and sucking on a piece.
- (Vincenzo) Yes
- (Joosung) Oh, I see.
It's scary, this file
Have you ever opened the file?
No, not yet
I saved the good stuff to watch together.
[laughter]
(Chayoung)
Yes, Mr. Secretary
oar, laptop, laptop, laptop
[Joosung’s urgent groan]
[Seunghyuk sighs]
(Seunghyuk)
Wow, something feels uncomfortable, huh?
Lee, on the deal with Prosecutor Jeong.
There must be major items.
He, he
That file was taken out of the gallery at that time.
You know that file, the file
Is that really the only one?
(Chinese book)
Hey, that's one thing, okay?
Strong enough, yeah
Plus, my brother evaded taxes, what, huh?
Illegal acquisition of stocks
Well, everything is included.
No, I feel like
I don't think there's just one.
(Chinese book)
No, then what?
Well, what is there...
[Interesting music]
What more is there?
[Seunghyuk mutters]
Oh, I can't think, I can't think.
(Seunghyuk)
Anyway
Prosecutor Jeong is now on the Chairman’s side.
[Meaningful music]
Because the transaction with Daechang Ilbo went well.
Now the Chairman is truly out of control.
I'm getting stronger
[sigh]
[Mouse click sound]
[Exciting music]
[Juseong’s elasticity]
(Chayoung)
Wow
Wow, celebrity Jirashi, go away!
It's enormous
(Joosung)
What is this?
It's almost a temple-level record, right?
This target is along with the barbell.
This is Daechang Ilbo.
(Chayoung)
Daechang Ilbo I was waiting for you
This trash media company, Mr.
(Joosung)
In the old days, we even wiped poop with newspaper.
There is no use for this damn newspaper anymore.
(Chayoung)
No, what kind of media company
Saying outrageous things 365 days a year
Say something rude or nothing
(Vincenzo)
Repeated nonsense is not a mistake, but an attitude.
It never changes
(Chayoung)
Even if only one piece disappears
I feel like my eyes and ears will become clearer
First of all, the two got into a fight
I plan on destroying each other.
Two of us
How do we fight?
(Chayoung)
For us
You have this guillotine file, right?
(Joosung)
The villain exploits the villain's weakness
[Vincenzo laughs slightly]
[A knocking sound is heard]
(Vincenzo)
Now
[The door clicks open]
[Lonely music]
[Embarrassed laughter]
(Chinese book)
Well, the atmosphere is very
It's messy and awkward and good, yes.
[Vincenzo laughs]
Why did you come here?
Well, he could come.
(Vincenzo)
Yeah
[Interesting music]
(Chinese book)
Well, no big deal, hey
The most expensive Luwak coffee in the world
Do you know Luwak coffee?
Luwak coffee, made from civet cat poop
It's so precious
(Joosung)
What kind of shit are you talking about?
Hey, what are you doing?
[Meaningful music]
(Myunghee)
Is Vincenzo really lucky?
Are you good at skills?
It's really amazing
15 tons gold on guillotine pile
guillotine file
Who knows if it's there
If you just get it
(Myunghee)
All the people in Korea who use their strength
I will kneel at your feet, Chairman.
Wow, it really looks like a ring from ‘The Lord of the Rings’.
(Myunghee)
Don't you know it when you watch the movie?
This absolute ring
If anyone gets involved, it will be a big problem.
Like the chairman or me
I have to meet the owner to do my job properly.
[Junwoo sighs]
First, let’s quickly destroy Geumga Plaza.
That way you can take out the guillotine file.
(Junwoo)
Ah, the gold that is there
I will also give you a lawyer.
yes
Thank you very much
[Hanseo rattles his chair]
(Vincenzo)
thank you
(Chayoung)
[Hanseo’s puzzled groan]
(Chinese book)
Uncle, uncle, uncle
Huh, I bought it
I'll bring you a cup of Luwak coffee.
What is this?
There is no coffee machine.
(Chinese book)
Wow, the environment is really poor.
[coughing]
Seed, it’s bitter.
Man, why is this so bitter?
[Hanseo clears his throat]
[Putting down the cup]
Oh my
Last time, I told my lawyer
I heard you asked me to deal with your brother?
So it would have been easy if you had listened to me back then.
We're lawyers
I took it out for no reason, and now it's much more difficult.
(Vincenzo)
Did I make it clear?
They don't take advantage of betrayal between family members.
Ha, I was in no mood at the time.
I couldn't speak
I'm not trying to betray you
[Interesting music]
(Chinese book)
I
Uh, so
- Prevent further slaughter
- (Vincenzo) Yes
(Chinese book)
I'm trying to run Babel legally.
(Chayoung)
I guess I've been studying a lot lately
My vocabulary has improved
[Laughs]
Yeah
(Vincenzo)
So get rid of my brother
Are you going to run the business normally?
(Chinese book)
That's it
(Vincenzo)
Yeah
I really love barbell
(Chinese book)
I want to try running a business properly.
Stop killing people
I'm really serious
(Chayoung)
Then you take care of it.
Why are you asking us?
That is
Ah, no matter how much I think about it,
There are only you
Someone who can beat my brother
(Vincenzo)
Well, my intentions are good.
Do you deserve it?
I'm taking a lot of business classes these days.
A lot of reading, just like that
(Chinese book)
Humanities, economics, everything you can see
I still want to read something, just
(Vincenzo)
Yeah
Then take the quiz here
Ah, what suddenly happened again...
(Chinese book)
Okay
Okay, okay
[Rhythmic music]
Well, take a look, take a look
[Chayoung clears her throat]
Adam Smith
As said in ‘The Wealth of Nations’
Bringing order to the market economy
What do you call this hand?
manners hands
Ding!
[Wrong answer sound effect]
invisible hand
[Rhythmic music]
(Vincenzo)
As the economy grows
in gross national product
The proportion of public sector spending is increasing.
What is this law?
[Snaps fingers]
Jung, law of the jungle
(Chayoung)
Ding!
[Wrong answer sound effect]
Wagner's Law
[Rhythmic music]
(Vincenzo)
This time the difficulty level is the lowest.
For companies to improve competitiveness
With innovative techniques learned from other companies,
This term comes from an iron rod?
Hint, bench?
bench, bench, bench press, bench press
(Chayoung)
Dang, benchmarking!
[Wrong answer sound effect]
(Vincenzo)
get out
(Chinese book)
No, no
[Interesting music]
Wasn't one correct?
[Vincenzo’s awkward laughter]
(Chayoung)
How can you not guess anything?
I think I have the right manners, don't I?
If you want our help
Come study more
(Vincenzo)
to join us
Must have an intellectual level
Oh, well, is this a conference or something? Why, why?
Don't if you don't like it
(Vincenzo)
get out
(Chinese book)
No, it's really ridiculous, what
Wait a minute, then, then
If I pass it next time I come back
really, really help
[Awkward laughter]
[Hanseo’s laughter]
(Vincenzo)
get out
I'm going because I'm really dirty, I'm going
(Chinese book)
What is the scope of the test?
(Vincenzo)
Get out, manager.
(Chinese book)
Uncle, did you know your manners? Manners hands?
[Joosung’s awkward laughter]
(Joosung)
This is manners
[Chayoung sighs]
Are you really going to accept Jang Hanseo?
(Vincenzo)
Um…
[Atmospheric music plays]
(Junwoo)
I want Vincenzo's life
You tried to steal it, right?
But Vincenzo
They're taking what I care about
RDU-90
BLSD
My Babel Tower
And in the gallery
My money!
[Myunghee clears her throat]
What should I take away?
Does it bother Vincenzo?
You have to take away something precious.
[Myunghee takes a breath]
(Myunghee)
Since death is the end of the world, it's not life, right?
If I had to pick it up,
Let’s take a look at old family relationships.
family?
[Meaningful music]
Is that valuable?
Normal people
I cherish my family
Oh, I see.
(Junwoo)
Ah, I was the only one who didn't know
[Laughs]
Then I'll have to do that.
[Interesting music]
[Joosung's labored breathing]
(Chayoung)
What's wrong with your face?
It's so fun
(Joosung)
I don't eat and I don't poop.
I watched it 24 hours a day
Briefing quickly
I'll go and see you again later.
(Vincenzo)
Hey, I still have to do my business.
Look at the file, manager.
Then the poison rises.
From The Guillotine Files
About Daechang Ilbo President Oh Jeong-bae
I checked the main contents.
What a bad guy.
What's the worst?
He is the murderer who killed my brother.
[laughter]
(Chayoung)
Daechang Ilbo is also quite good.
Why are all these brothers enemies of Cheolcheon?
Why did you kill your brother?
There's a fight over the successor.
But the charges were completely cleared.
[Exciting music]
[Running steps]
(Joosung)
I went hiking with my brother.
[Boss Oh’s surprised groan]
Killed by pushing him off a cliff
[crow crying]
(Vincenzo)
There would have been no witnesses.
What about proof of murder?
(Joosung)
Ecological surveillance cameras nearby
Filming has been completed
But this recording is not from the police.
From the Foreign Security Intelligence Service
Got it first
(Chayoung)
Foreign security intelligence agency
Using this as a weakness
Oh, I made a deal with the boss.
yes
(Heesu)
He's just such a piece of shit.
How could you kill my brother, huh?
(Joosung)
Did you hear everything?
[Interesting music]
(Heesu)
Can I hear whispers better?
[Heesu’s laughter]
[Vincenzo’s surprised gasp]
Don't worry, keep your mouth shut.
[Zipper sound effect]
Shhh!
Manager, is there anything else special?
[Exciting music]
(Joosung)
A shaman who blindly believes and follows
There is one person
Complete ten months
In front of a young child about to achieve success...
(Joosung)
All major and minor decisions
I do whatever the shaman tells me to do.
[Muryeong is ringing]
All housework and work
But this shaman
Former pseudo cult leader
I have 4 convictions for fraud and sexual harassment.
Of course, President Oh doesn’t know.
Man, this is so ridiculous.
What kind of person would you ask about fate?
People are the original
What I don't know the most
Because I believe in it the most.
Is he a scammer or a brave man?
I'll have to check it out.
[Juseong slurps]
[Puts down chopsticks]
I'll go and see
[Biryu’s moans]
(Cheolwook)
Oh my, oh my, oh my
[Biryu’s moans]
[Moaning in pain]
Oh my
[Kiseok’s elasticity]
(Kiseok)
As expected, the Daechang Ilbo newspaper
They say it looks the most flammable
(Cheolwook)
The world's useless newspapers
They say I have to use it as firewood.
(Biryu)
Hey, who are you guys?
(Cheolwook)
Who is it?
I brought you here to discuss the fate of my business trip.
What?
[A clicking sound is heard]
[Exciting music]
(Biryu)
Hey, who are you again?
(Vincenzo)
Our Biryu is
[Vincenzo turns on the lighter]
Burns to death in 5 minutes
Do we know the truth?
[Blows loudly]
(Cheolwook)
Of course you would know, right?
He is a brave shaman.
(Kiseok)
Under the roof after it burned down
Do you even know that it's going to fall?
(Vincenzo)
You know, he's a brave person.
[Blows out air]
Please save me
But you can change your fate again
Isn't it?
That's right, just do as I tell you.
[Kiseok’s groan of approval]
Why are you doing this, teachers?
[Vincenzo takes a breath]
(Vincenzo)
But do customers know?
This guy is a cult leader and a fraudster.
He has 4 previous convictions for sexual harassment.
Write, I guess.
I don't know that yet, sir.
(Vincenzo)
So, shall we start talking now?
huh?
after!
- (Cheolwook) Bitter, should I pour it?
- (Kiseok) Light it on fire?
(Vincenzo)
Now, let’s start with a moment of silence for our deceased.
Let's get started
- (Cheolwook) Oh, is that so?
- yes?
(Vincenzo)
Now, a moment of silence for the deceased.
[devotional music]
No, don't meditate
Why are you doing this?
(Vincenzo)
Okay, okay, let's get started.
[Exciting music]
(Cheolwook)
Lift your leg, lift your leg
- You have to pour it from the head, first from the head.
- (Vincenzo) From the head?
- no…
- (Cheolwook) This is kerosene.
I meant to talk.
- (non-class) no
- (Vincenzo) Now, fire, fire, fire
- (Bryu) No, let me talk, no.
- (Vincenzo) Daechang Ilbo, Daechang Ilbo
[Biryu’s laughter]
[Blows loudly]
[Cheolwook’s surprised groan]
Oh, it's on fire, it's on fire
Oh, it's on fire, hoo!
(Kiseok)
Come on!
[Tense sound effect]
Fuck the barbell and the large intestine
for your project
Who will play the role of a shaman?
We will select you by vote.
[People cheering]
The one person most suited to being a shaman
Please choose
[Exciting music]
Now
Who among us, who among us
The vote on whether to play the role of a shaman has been completed.
(Kiseok)
Now let's start counting the votes.
[People cheering]
'Vincenzo'
[People's elasticity]
[Interesting music]
(Vincenzo)
Me? Who is playing pranks again?
[Cheolwook’s laughter]
[Tap Jooseong]
Chee, manager.
Did you see it?
(Kiseok)
‘Attorney Vincenzo’
[Seokdo’s laughter]
‘I love Vincenzo Casanova’s corn salad’
(Vincenzo)
No…
[Seokdo and Sunam giggle]
Are you laughing?
(Kiseok)
'Jovinsen'
[People cheering]
- 'Vintamin Senzo'
- (Vincenzo) No, why me...
- 'Mr. Bean'
- (Vincenzo) What’s wrong with everyone?
(Kiseok)
'Empty stool', 'Jovinsen', 'Vincenzo'
- (Vincenzo) Everyone
- (Kiseok) ‘Attorney Vincenzo’
[Seokdo’s laughter]
[sigh]
(Kiseok)
‘Jovinsen’, ‘Vincenzo Quasano’
[People's elasticity]
(Yeonjin)
'Gwasano'
Vincenzo, right? ‘Attorney Vincenzo’
[Tense sound effect]
(Kiseok)
Now
This is the last remaining vote
Ah, that last vote
Is there a need to count votes?
Vincennes… 'Hong Cha-young'
[Humorous sound effects]
[People laughing]
(Chayoung)
Baby, why me again?
Cassano said that, right?
(Kiseok)
Come on!
[Exciting music]
Attorney Vincenzo plays the role of the shaman.
elected
[People cheering]
(people)
Vincenzo! Vincenzo! Vincenzo!
Vincenzo! Vincenzo!
[Meaningful music]
[laughter]
[Call connection tone]
Ah, yes, Biryu.
[Laughs slightly]
Well, I have a quick question to ask you.
Yes?
What do you mean by that?
Mr. Biryu
[Ancient music]
I can no longer serve God
The mountain god left me
(President Oh)
No, I need Biryu.
Well, please cheer up
Mr. Biryu
- Oh boss, listen to me carefully.
- (President Oh) Yes
yes
I'm tired now
[Interesting music]
(Biryu)
Instead, there is one very brave person.
no, no
The abilities he possessed
You're much stronger than me
No, no, huh?
You have to go to him.
That's how we both live
[People are murmuring]
- (in advance) Next time?
- (Yeonjin) Oh my gosh
(Hongsik)
You have to do this for 5 minutes per person.
- (Yeonjin) Oh, they say you’re really good at it.
- (Hongsik) Draw it?
(Yeonjin)
uh
- (Yeonjin) Ugh
- (In advance) I'm dying of curiosity.
(Yeonjin)
I mean, wait over an hour.
How many times, uncle?
[nervous music]
- (Larry Kang) Number 4.
- (Yeonjin) Oh
- (in advance) I am number 6
[Clears cough]
(people)
Huh?
(Yeonjin)
Don't cut in line, man.
(Hongsik)
Ah, where do I go now?
Can't you see I'm waiting?
- (Yeonjin) Yes
- Take the number ticket, wayu
(in advance)
That's right, we're all like this
People are waiting after receiving a number.
[Interesting music]
(Yeonjin)
Look, look, like this, huh?
[People respond]
I made a reservation, right?
[Yeonjin’s surprised gasp]
(Yeonjin)
Oh, really?
[People moan in agreement]
Oh, is there anything like that?
Ah, then you should go in quickly.
[Yeonjin’s laughter]
Wow, I'm jealous
- (Larry Kang) Wow, that would be nice.
- (in advance) Come
(in advance)
Jjang
[People's elasticity]
[President Oh clears his throat]
- (in advance) It would be really nice
- (Yeonjin) Wow
- (Cheolwook) Wow, I’m jealous.
- (Yeonjin) Fighting
[Miri’s elasticity]
[Meaningful music]
How did you get here?
Ah, yes
I came to Daechang through the introduction of Biryu…
Daechang
Welcome
Master Yeorim is waiting.
Ah, yes
[Clears cough]
[President Oh takes off his shoes]
[President Oh clears his throat]
[Emphasized sound effect]
[Ancient music]
The name of the shrine is
[laughter]
How fun is that?
He was a Yeonguijeong during the Joseon Dynasty.
Teacher Seolhwa Park Hyo
(Joosung)
He went into the mountains and realized the Tao.
And you became a hermit
So the God we serve
This is Park Hyo-shin
[President Oh giggles]
[Humorous sound effects]
[President Oh’s laughter]
[President Oh takes a deep breath]
(President Oh)
Ah, yes, I see.
(Joosung)
♪ It got longer before I knew it ♪
[Chayoung goes to eat]
[takes a breath]
Well, I kinda
(President Oh)
I came because there are things I want to know.
Well, I wonder if I can ask.
Shall I ask?
Should I not?
get out
I have nothing to say to someone who is going to die anyway.
[President Oh taps the table]
Look at this!
[Savoring moans]
[Puts down the glass]
Since this is my first meeting, there is no need to send condolences.
(President Oh)
No, you know who I am
These scammers, ha, tsk
Jeongbae
[Meaningful music]
What?
‘Jeongbae’?
[Bubble sound effect]
(President Oh)
You bastard, how dare you name someone!
[Dark sound effect]
(Vincenzo)
I'm your brother, Jeongbae.
[Ancient music]
What?
[Chayoung’s trembling moans]
(Vincenzo)
I'm so cold
[trembling moan]
[Vincenzo’s trembling groan]
Oh my, it's cold
Hand, hand...
[Vincenzo blows lightly]
Ugh, it's cold.
[Bubble sound effect]
[Vincenzo’s trembling groan]
[Blows repeatedly]
Drop it off the cliff
What if I just go?
I'm still here, huh?
[eerie sound effect]
[nervous music]
[President Oh’s trembling breathing]
[President Oh’s surprised gasp]
(President Oh)
How…
how here
(Vincenzo)
Uh, it's cold, uh, it's cold
[trembling moan]
[Bubble sound effect]
[Thumps the prize]
Bring me up quickly, Jeongbae.
I'm so cold, huh?
I'm so cold, Jeongbae
(President Oh)
Go away, go away, go away!
- (Vincenzo) Jeong Bae-ya
- (Boss Oh) Please go away!
[Music that heightens tension]
Go away!
[Vincenzo’s trembling groan]
Go away, go away!
(Vincenzo)
Jeongbae, Jeongbae, Jeongbae
[President Oh’s frightened groan]
Go away, go away!
(Vincenzo)
Jeongbae, Jeongbae, it’s so cold, Jeongbae
Jeongbae, it’s so cold
[President Oh’s scream]
[President Oh’s trembling breathing]
(President Oh)
my destiny
[Vincenzo puts down his glass]
Why is it so heavy?
fate is not heavy
you are weak
(President Oh)
Yes?
The weaker I am, the weaker I am.
Because fate becomes heavier that much.
Ah, yes
what is killing you
Do you want to see it?
yes, i miss you
[Interesting music]
[Bubble sound effect]
[Music that heightens the mood]
[Tense sound effect]
[Meaningful music]
[surprised gasp]
If you don't break up with Babel
you will die miserably
[shaking breathing]
Can I just quit the kite?
Don't just cut ties
You have to break it by thoroughly stepping on the barbell.
Yes?
Only then can the fluid be completely removed.
(President Oh)
It's not that easy
(Vincenzo)
Ah, tsk tsk, tsk tsk
[Ancient music]
[Slams down the fan]
[Humorous sound effects]
[Vincenzo’s elasticity]
[Vincenzo clicks his tongue repeatedly]
It's the last day of your life
[Dark sound effect]
[Bubble sound effect]
5 days
[Ancient music]
[surprised moan]
[Embarrassed groan]
Ugh, pity me, ugh, pity me
[President Oh’s trembling breathing]
[Chayoung’s powerful moans]
[Chayoung hums]
[Vincenzo’s light sigh]
[Laughs]
(Chayoung)
no
I was too strong earlier
My arm hurts, it hurts so much
[Chayoung sighs]
No, but isn't it so funny?
The president of a media company that only deals with facts
You're doing this because you're superstitious.
[laughter]
Because I'm not interested in facts
You're obsessed with superstition.
[Joosung’s surprised groan]
(Vincenzo)
Oh, what a surprise.
That's right
(Joosung)
[Snaps fingers]
I'm so crazy today
There's something I couldn't tell you
About Chairman Jang Han-seok
Here's a surprising fact
It's in the guillotine file.
What is it?
(Joosung)
Chairman Jang Han-seok
Middle and high school days
Killed 4 classmates
[Meaningful music]
A classmate you don't like
Call them to the rooftop and make them jump, or
As if summoned to the mountain at night to hunt
Track them down and kill them
the other one
When playing soccer during PE class
Just because he stole the ball
Strangled with a goal net
[laughter]
What's scarier is
[Crying all night]
[Student groans in pain]
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Music that heightens the mood]
(Joosung)
They took the dead children's watches.
As a keepsake and trophy.
And proud of it
I even talked to people around me.
No, isn't this really crazy?
열여섯 살 때
사이코패스 판정을 받았답니다
그래서 아버지가 미국으로 보낸 거네요
[의미심장한 음악]
진짜 연쇄 살인마가 될까 봐
(주성)
동생 장한서는
형의 구타와 가혹 행위 때문에
어릴 때부터 줄곧
정신과 치료를 받았습니다
그러다 결국 마약까지 손을 댔고요
아무리 그래도 마약에 손을 대고 그래
아유, 이놈의 새끼, 씨
어쨌든 아버지 장국환 회장이
모든 사건을 돈으로 막고
비밀에 부친 거죠
쉽지 않은 상대였던 이유가 있었네요
괴물 중의 괴물
[어두운 음악]
[준우의 떨리는 숨소리]
[통화 연결음]
[어이없는 웃음]
[휴대전화 진동음]
(오 사장)
여보세요
도대체 뭐 하신 거예요?
What is this, man?
(President Oh)
Chairman Jang
According to our company's overall press guidelines,
There has been a change
Have I done something to upset you?
(President Oh)
Hey, there's nothing like that.
Now our Daechang Ilbo
This is a media company that only reports the truth.
Truth?
(Junwoo)
The most corrupt media company in Korea
The truth?
Is it a bit difficult to say?
That's how you manage it properly, tsk!
Stop hanging up!
[Call end sound]
Uncle, uncle
Hey!
[Bubble sound effect]
[Dark sound effect]
[sigh]
(President Oh)
No, why still
[Vincenzo opens the lighter]
Are there any numbers left, yes?
I hit the barbell very harshly.
That's not enough to save your life
Yes?
[Vincenzo clicks the lighter shut]
(President Oh)
So what else should I do!
Master of Babel, King of Babel
[Meaningful music]
Maybe
Are you talking about Chairman Jang Han-seok?
(Vincenzo)
That person is holding your juices
informing of the person's past evil deeds
Because of that person, I wander the nine heavens
For the souls
Those spirits will help you
If you wander the Nine Heavens...
[shaking breathing]
[President Oh’s urgent breathing]
(President Oh)
Did Han Seok kill anyone?
[Bubble sound effect]
[bizarre moans]
[eerie music]
[surprised moan]
[Vincenzo’s bizarre groan]
[President Oh’s surprised groan]
[Ancient music]
[Bubble sound effect]
Han Seok-ah
i was wrong
don't hit me
(Vincenzo)
Hanseok, I was wrong, I was wrong
[Joosung’s painful moans]
I'll pray like this
That's not Han Seok
(President Oh)
That's not Han Seok.
don't strangle me
- (Vincenzo) I’m suffocating, I feel like I’m going to die.
- (Chayoung) Jang Han-seok
(Vincenzo)
Don't strangle me, I'm suffocating
(Chayoung)
Jang Han-seok, save me
please don't do that
(President Oh)
It's not one seat.
That's not Han Seok!
(Vincenzo)
This is my watch, this is my watch
[President Oh’s frightened groan]
This is my watch, this is my watch, my watch
[Frightened groan]
(Anchor on TV)
Is the chairman of Korea's leading Babel Group a school abuser?
[Interesting music plays on TV]
No, he is the main culprit of the massacre?
This is truly shocking.
Because that's not enough
without any punishment
He continued to rise to his current position as chairman?
[Junwoo’s laughter]
No, what the hell
Over the years, prosecutors and police
What were they doing?
What the…
(Anchor on TV)
Now many people
[sigh]
[Junwoo’s laughter]
On various portal bulletin boards and petition bulletin boards
Punishment of this murderer Chairman
I'm urging
Ha, write
[The anchor on TV continues speaking]
[Meaningful music]
How on earth did you know?
(Junwoo)
No matter how old you are
You don't know my childhood
(Anchor on TV)
We will continue to report on this situation.
Currently, Babel Group is…
Hey, isn't that you?
What do you mean, brother?
Not me
(Chinese book)
No, in the article
I'm crazy too
They even called me a drug addict.
Would that be me?
Well, that's true
In the past, I also heard about the Chairman’s incident.
They say there was no coverage.
Anyone who knows this
Who else is there?
father
Detective at the time
(Junwoo)
Prosecutor at the time
[English]
They're all dead now
(Myunghee)
[Korean]
If so
we don't expect
There must be an information line
The problem is intent
President Oh Jeong-bae
Why is it suddenly like this?
It looks like you're rushing to kill me now?
[camera shutter sound]
[Calm music]
[Gong sound effect]
“To live”
[President Oh’s heavy breathing]
[President Oh’s trembling breathing]
[shaking breathing]
That's it now
you saved your life
[President Oh’s urgent breathing]
Fate is weak in front of the brave.
The law is strong in the face of the weak
You did it bravely, yes
(Vincenzo)
Yeah
[Sobbing]
[upbeat music]
(President Oh)
[Sobbing]
thank you
[Meaningful music]
[breathes and then exhales]
[sigh]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
It's been a while, boss.
Can I see you now?
I'm going to the plaza.
See you in the parking lot
Yes, you do.
yes
[Car door slams shut]
[Oncoming car engine sound]
[nervous music]
[Gangman 1’s spirit]
[Fight noisily]
[President Cho’s groans of difficulty]
[Gangman 1’s spirit]
[Rough breathing]
[The spirit of the two strangers]
[intense music]
[The screams of the monsters]
[Gangster 3’s frightened groans]
[Gangster 3’s groans of difficulty]
[The knife falls with a clink]
(Ghost 3)
Hey, bounce!
No, what are they doing?
(President Cho)
Perhaps Prosecutor Jeong
Looks like the people who sent it
[President Cho sighs]
Prosecutor Jeong?
[Meaningful music]
(Myunghee)
It was as expected
Vincenzo was joking.
blindly trusting the words of a shaman
Oh, using the boss.
(Junwoo)
Really detailed
The mafia really can't be beat.
[Junwoo laughs]
By the way
How did they know this information about my childhood?
(Myunghee)
Well, I have my doubts about that too.
if there is a possibility
It is a foreign security information source.
How on earth did they know?
Considering the current situation
Babel and Daechang
I think they caused them to collide with each other
Anyway, Mr. Jeongbae of Daechang Ilbo
You can't do that to me.
What should I do?
Let's get Vincenzo to end this conflict.
(Myunghee)
Oh, I have one thing to show you.
(Junwoo)
What is it?
(Myunghee)
Vincenzo's Korean name is Park Joo-hyung.
Abandoned by my mother when I was young
I was adopted
[heavy music]
Is your mom alive?
I'm alive
I recently got out of prison.
Because of pancreatic cancer.
Why in prison?
Shinkwang Finance Chairman Hwang Deok-bae
This is the helper regarding the death incident.
(Junwoo)
Wait a minute
You messed up the last agreement ceremony.
Is that how it's connected?
(Myunghee)
That's right
At the time of the incident, lawyer Hong Yoo-chan
I was a public defender.
But today, regarding the Chairman Hwang Deok-bae incident,
A request for reconsideration has been made
Retrial?
[smiling slightly]
Who?
Hong Cha-young
Of course, Vincenzo will be behind him.
Are you saying Vincenzo is meeting his mother?
(Myunghee)
The hospital where Vincenzo’s biological mother is currently located.
We are investigating the location
[Vincenzo clicks his lighter]
[Meaningful music]
With Prosecutor Jeong 5 years ago
We met at the Foreign Security Intelligence Service.
(President Cho)
Prosecutor Jeong was a dispatched prosecutor.
I had a part-time job
Then we
I found out the true nature of the Guillotine File.
Prosecutor Jeong said with that file,
All corruption in Korea
I thought I could eradicate it.
So I tried to get my hands on it somehow.
I also agreed with Prosecutor Jeong.
[Vincenzo opens the lighter]
He was a just prosecutor back then, right?
(President Cho)
yes
Afterwards, the file was hacked and disappeared.
I volunteered for the team looking for the files
So we've come this far
However, currently Prosecutor Jeong
Did you betray me?
Yes, actually for the past few months
I had a bad feeling
(President Cho)
Prosecutor Jeong talks about the guillotine file
I think I have other desires.
Tsk, bitter
Now that I'm on the same side as Jang Han-seok
I guess you also found out about Jang Han-seok.
(Vincenzo)
Guillotine file and crack
It's here
(President Cho)
Together
You have to tear down the building
And you know you can take it out
Tsk
[President Cho sighs]
[sigh]
[Calm music]
[Rustling papers]
[Meaningful sound effects]
[nervous music]
[Vincenzo’s heavy breathing]
(Vincenzo)
IC
[Vincenzo’s heavy breathing]
[The sound of the door squeaking is heard]
[Rough breathing]
[Meaningful music]
(Detective)
Mr. Vincenzo Cassano
To you, President Oh Jeong-bae
Arrested for murder
[sigh]
[Rhythmic music]
(Chayoung)
You fell into a trap, right?
(Junwoo)
Then we should use the most effective method.
I need to keep them from finding it forever.
(Vincenzo)
I have to find the guy who lured me in first.
All the people who tried to raise the Tower of Babel
I'm going to judge you
(Myunghee)
Vincenzo leads Korea
You can also flip it over
[camera shutter sound]
(Junwoo)
To preserve Geumga Plaza as a part of history
(Chayoung)
Please make sure to pay for it
(Vincenzo)
you have to die now
Slowly feeling the stages of pain
death
Subtitle: Kwon Jeong-won